Guide to the Watkins Loomis Records,
Rare Book and Manuscript Library Columbia University Libraries
- Series IX: Arranged Correspondence
  - Guillermoprieto, Alma (Box 23)
  - H miscellaneous (Box 24)
  - Hadfield, Alice Mary (Box 24)
  - Haldeman, Pat (Box 24)
  - Harvard Medical Letter (Box 24)
  - Harvard Medical Magazine (Box 24)
  - Hauptman, William (Box 25)
  - Hawk, David (Box 25)
  - Hazleton, Leslie (Box 26)
  - Hedren, Tippi (Box 27)
  - Heffernan, William (Box 27)
  - Hingham, David (Box 27)
  - Hirschfeld, Neal (Box 28)
  - Howard, Maureen (Box 28)
  - Howell, Barbara (Box 28)
  - I miscellaneous (Box 29)
  - J miscellaneous (Box 29)
  - Jones, Stacey (Box 29)
  - K miscellaneous (Box 29)
  - Kaufman (Box 30)
  - Kavaler, Lucy (Box 30)
  - King, David (Box 30)
  - Kotker, Zane (Box 30)
  - Krauss, Clifford (Box 31)
  - L miscellaneous (Box 31)
  - Lake, Canton (Box 31)
  - Lake, Carlton (Box 32)
  - Lanes, Selma (Box 32)
  - Leckie, Robert (Box 32)
  - Lehman, John (Box 32)
  - Levi, Vicki (Box 32)
  - Levin, Donna (Box 32)
  - Levy, Francis (Box 32)
  - Lewis, RW.B. (Box 32)
  - Little Literary Magazines (Box 33)
  - Loeser, Katinka (Box 33)
  - Loomis, Gloria (Box 33)
  - M miscellaneous (Box 33)
  - Mc miscellaneous (Box 33)
  - McCann, Hugh Wray (Box 34)
  - McKee, Cameron (Box 34)
  - McKibber, Bill (Box 34)
  - McQuown, Judith (Box 34)
  - Maddux, Rachel (Box 34)
  - Maharidge, Dale (Box 34)
  - Malouf, Pyrra (Box 34)
  - Mann, Charles (Box 34)
  - Marcus, G.J. (Box 34)
  - Markham, Beryl (Box 34)
  - Maudlin, Bill (Box 34)
  - Mayer, Debby (Box 35)
  - Mayer. Musa (Box 35)
  - Mazer, Gwen (Box 35)
  - Mernit, Susan (Box 35)
  - Michelmore, Peter (Box 35)
  - Moorehead, Alan (Box 35)
  - Morgan, Seth (Box 35)
  - Morrison, Alan (Box 35)
  - Movie lists current (Box 35)
  - N miscellaneous (Box 36)
  - O miscellaneous (Box 36)
  - Ogilvie, Elizabeth (Box 36)
  - Ogilvie, Gordon (Box 36)
  - O'Kun, Lan (Box 36)
  - Owens, Carole (Box 36)
  - Owens, Louis (Box 36)
  - P miscellaneous (Box 37)
  - Perera, Victor (Box 37)
  - Perlez, Jane (Box 37)
  - Piirto, John (Box 37)
  - Plimmer, Charlotte & Dennis (Box 38)
  - Pollinger, Laurence (Box 38)
  - Pollinger, Murray (Box 38)
  - Post, Chuck (Box 38)
  - Prince, Francine & Harold (Box 38)
  - Pritchard, William (Box 38)
  - Probst, Mark (Box 38)
  - Production companies (Box 38)
  - Publishing information (Box 38)
  - Q miscellaneous (Box 39)
  - R miscellaneous (Box 39)
  - Ratray, David (Box 39)
  - Ray, Carlton (Box 40)
  - Resumes (Box 40)
  - Reuther, Elisabeth (Box 40)
  - Richardson, John (Box 40)
  - Roach, Janet (Box 40)
  - Robinson, Barbara (Box 40)
  - Rohde, Barbara (Box 40)
  - Romance tip sheets (Box 40)
  - Rossant, Colette (Box 40)
  - Rose, Barbara (Box 40)
  - Rosen, Norma (Box 41)
  - Rosenblatt, Roger (Box 41)
  - Rutman, Leo (Box 41)
  - S miscellaneous (Box 42)
  - Salk, Jonas (Box 42)
  - Sandoval, Judith (Box 42)
  - Sandrow, Nahma (Box 42)
  - Satz, Arthur (Box 42)
  - Sayers, Dorothy (Box 43)
  - Sayle, Tessa
  - Scarpitti, F. & A. Block (Box 43)
  - Schwartz, Jane (Box 44)
  - Schwartzman, Bill (Box 44)
  - Seager, Alan (Box 44)
  - Sealy, Shirley (Box 44)
  - Shafer, Jack (Box 44)
  - Shubik, Irene (Box 44)
  - Skalkin-Smith, Leora (Box 44)
  - Smith Joseph Burgholzer (Box 44)
  - Smith, Wayne (Box 44)
  - Scouts (foreign) (Box 45)
  - Sommer, Scott (Box 45)
  - Spunt, George (Box 45)
  - Stahl, Sam (Box 45)
  - Stein, Toby (Box 45)
  - Storm, Hyemeyohsts (Box 45)
  - Strasser, Julie (Box 45)
  - Styron, Rose (Box 45)
  - Swarthout, Glendon (Box 45)
  - T miscellaneous (Box 46)
  - Taylor, Theodore (Box 46)
  - Taylor, Theodore (1983-) (Box 47)
  - Tax Information (Box 47)
  - Tey, Josephine (Box 48)
  - Thomson, David (Box 48)
  - Trachtenberg, Peter (Box 48)
  - Train (Box 48)
  - Travers, P.L. (Box 48)
  - U miscellaneous (Box 48)
  - V miscellaneous (Box 49)
  - Vavra, Robert (1979-1982) (Box 49)
  - Vavra, Robert (1983-) (Box 50)
  - Vita, Trisha (Box 50)
  - Vivante, Arthur (Box 50)
  - W miscellaneous (Box 51)
  - Watkins Inc. (Box 51)
  - Watkins, Mike (Box 51)
  - Watkins Loomis (Box 51)
  - Watkins Loomis Employees (Box 52)
  - Watt, A.P. (Box 52)
  - Webb, Marilyn (Box 52)
  - Weber, Nicholas Fox (Box 52)
  - Weissberg, Michael (Box 52)
  - Weissman, Gerald (Box 52)
  - Wharton, Edith (estate) (Box 53)
  - Wharton/Lewis (Box 54)
  - Whiton, Sherrill (Box 55)
  - Williams, Charles (Box 55)
  - Williamson, Bruce (Box 55)
  - Winn, David (Box 55)
  - Yankowitz, Susan (Box 56)
  - Yorinks, Arthur (Box 56)
  - XYZ misc. (Box 56)
  - Zakaria, Ralig (Box 56)
- Series X: Arranged Manuscripts
  The arranged manuscript section consists of photocopies of Seth Morgan's Homeboy as well as photocopies of an unlinised and unpublished (due to Morgan's death) manuscrpt tentatively titled Mardi Gras. There are two sets divided into boxes as follows:
  - Morgan, Seth Homeboy [1st set] (Box 57-59)
  - Morgan, Seth Homeboy [2nd set] (Box 60 -65)
  - Morgan, Seth Mardi Gras (Box 66-67)
- Series XI: Arranged Documents
  - Lewis, Sinclair Photocopies of contracts (Box 68)
  - Wooodswoman by Anne LaBastille -- Fame is the Spur by Howard Spring -- War Supplement by Philip Dorf -- The Two Philosophies: Atomism and Patterns by L.L. Whyte -- Bodies in Motion by Zane Kotker -- Freighter by Susan Yorke (Box 69)